I had actually spoken to my agent and my agent went around town looking for, you know, kind of like who wanted to do my next special.
And they was not with your girl.
OK, they was not with your girl.
And I'm not going to take that personal, but it was very like, yeah, we're doing this already.
So we can't or yeah, we already got these from these people.
So we can't or yeah, we could do it, but we're going to pay you 225 cents to do it.
And it was like, I just don't see the feasibility of me doing this in this fashion.
Like, it just feels like it's not really like the best way to go about things when it came down to it.
And this is why I love my agent. Shout out to Matt Horowitz.
He was just like, listen, if you have the means to do it yourself, I think you should.
I think we've stepped into a new era.
And I think that ultimately you as a creative work best when you are unfettered.
And unless the money is going to be worth it, the creative freedom is going to be worth it.